<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Four Sore Eyes</title>
    <link>https://BarryElderwine.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Four Sore Eyes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://BarryElderwine.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Eye Rubbing</title>
      <link>https://BarryElderwine.github.io/posts/eye-rub/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://BarryElderwine.github.io/posts/eye-rub/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m going to use this as a public hare brain short post approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Made with Natural and Artificial Flavors: Consciousness Part 1 of ...</title>
      <link>https://BarryElderwine.github.io/posts/consciousness-made-with-natural-and-artificial-flavors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://BarryElderwine.github.io/posts/consciousness-made-with-natural-and-artificial-flavors/</guid>
      <description>Willful Hedging It&amp;rsquo;s hard to tell anymore what the trends are in pop-sci-culture with the way we are fed content via the machines. I&amp;rsquo;ve had a whole lot of &amp;ldquo;free will&amp;rdquo; pushed into my online notice in recent weeks. Much of this content is related to the proposition of purposelessness that Robert Sapolsky has made with his book Determined. I did listen to this Audible book a couple months back, and presumably the machines are well aware of that, and as such are willing this related content in my direction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Write out in the open</title>
      <link>https://BarryElderwine.github.io/posts/write-out-in-the-open/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://BarryElderwine.github.io/posts/write-out-in-the-open/</guid>
      <description>Reasoning &amp;lsquo;A Site Four Sore Eyes&amp;rsquo; This is place where I can publish my ideas for the audience of me. I have an ever growing number of thixotropic reasons for setting up this platform. Probably the greatest overarching argument is to give me a place where I can air out my most persistent ruminations. This, in my fuzzy uncheckable logic, might - just might - provide some time and virtual space between my, in-this-moment thoughts, and my many-later-moments reconsiderations, allowing me to take them in with fresher, or simply differently focused eyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://BarryElderwine.github.io/be-getting-organized-through-chemistry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://BarryElderwine.github.io/be-getting-organized-through-chemistry/</guid>
      <description>The chemistry of getting organized
The chemistry of tribalism
The gamification of media Personal reality is subjective
Long-term thinking must be objective
The chemistry of long-term thinking Itʼs complicated.
Dopamine canʼt explain everything and oxytocin canʼt connect everything
Dogma works when it goes unchallenged by life experience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://BarryElderwine.github.io/be.001-insurrection-i%CA%BCm-struggling-to-get-motivated./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://BarryElderwine.github.io/be.001-insurrection-i%CA%BCm-struggling-to-get-motivated./</guid>
      <description>Yesterdayʼs events really knocked me down. Saddest part to me is that most of those people protesting, I believe, were well intentioned people, thinking they were doing the right and necessary thing. No doubt there were some, maybe even many, truly deplorable people involved, but the majority were trying to do what they believed was the best thing for this country. And there was very little acknowledgement of that, at least in the sources I get my news from.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://BarryElderwine.github.io/be.002-kinetics-of-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://BarryElderwine.github.io/be.002-kinetics-of-action/</guid>
      <description>Dimensions of response • Time of pain-reward vs response • Kinetic landscape • What are the parameters that describe that landscape?..</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://BarryElderwine.github.io/be.003-one-can-only-imagine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://BarryElderwine.github.io/be.003-one-can-only-imagine/</guid>
      <description>BE.003 One can only imagine One can only imagine within the limits of their experience. We are living in what appears to be the most divided moment in US History. In this statement of course Iʼm referring to the history since the beginning of the formation of the republic. It feels bold to suggest that we are now more divide than we were prior to and during the civil war and I may very well change my mind after more understanding to shift that timeline to the beginning of the Reconstruction era which may still seem too bold, but I believe the coming months, post “Insurrection” will bear more information on this point.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
